{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078938669","data":{"timestamp":" 947078938669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078939062","data":{"timestamp":" 947078939061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078939555","data":{"timestamp":" 947078939554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078939910","data":{"timestamp":" 947078939909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078940326","data":{"timestamp":" 947078940326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078940811","data":{"timestamp":" 947078940810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078941046","data":{"timestamp":" 947078941045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078944253","data":{"timestamp":" 947078944253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078944300","data":{"timestamp":" 947078944300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078945027","data":{"timestamp":" 947078945027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078945434","data":{"timestamp":" 947078945433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078945740","data":{"timestamp":" 947078945739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078945954","data":{"timestamp":" 947078945953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078946164","data":{"timestamp":" 947078946163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078946492","data":{"timestamp":" 947078946492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078946733","data":{"timestamp":" 947078946732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078949892","data":{"timestamp":" 947078949891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078950304","data":{"timestamp":" 947078950303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078952931","data":{"timestamp":" 947078952931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078953147","data":{"timestamp":" 947078953145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078953360","data":{"timestamp":" 947078953359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078956892","data":{"timestamp":" 947078956891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078960654","data":{"timestamp":" 947078960654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078961688","data":{"timestamp":" 947078961688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078964422","data":{"timestamp":" 947078964422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078964815","data":{"timestamp":" 947078964814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078965309","data":{"timestamp":" 947078965308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078965660","data":{"timestamp":" 947078965660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966075","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966560","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966794","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078970016","data":{"timestamp":" 947078970015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078970054","data":{"timestamp":" 947078970054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078970781","data":{"timestamp":" 947078970780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078971197","data":{"timestamp":" 947078971196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078971503","data":{"timestamp":" 947078971502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078971720","data":{"timestamp":" 947078971720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078971927","data":{"timestamp":" 947078971926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078972253","data":{"timestamp":" 947078972253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078972489","data":{"timestamp":" 947078972488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078975123","data":{"timestamp":" 947078975121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078975226","data":{"timestamp":" 947078975226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" f0a0ceed-2678-422d-ae29-5176a182b9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079005116","data":{"timestamp":" 947079005116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079009796","data":{"timestamp":" 947079009795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079011360","data":{"timestamp":" 947079011360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079015366","data":{"timestamp":" 947079015366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079016992","data":{"timestamp":" 947079016991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079022443","data":{"timestamp":" 947079022442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079024056","data":{"timestamp":" 947079024056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079028547","data":{"timestamp":" 947079028546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079030180","data":{"timestamp":" 947079030179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079034644","data":{"timestamp":" 947079034642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079036255","data":{"timestamp":" 947079036254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079043858","data":{"timestamp":" 947079043858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079045482","data":{"timestamp":" 947079045481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079063272","data":{"timestamp":" 947079063271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079064920","data":{"timestamp":" 947079064919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079068263","data":{"timestamp":" 947079068263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" START_TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079069392","data":{"timestamp":" 947079069392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079071003","data":{"timestamp":" 947079071002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079075995","data":{"timestamp":" 947079075995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079077595","data":{"timestamp":" 947079077595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079092587","data":{"timestamp":" 947079092587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079093634","data":{"timestamp":" 947079093633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079096454","data":{"timestamp":" 947079096454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079099319","data":{"timestamp":" 947079099319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079100890","data":{"timestamp":" 947079100890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079102897","data":{"timestamp":" 947079102896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079104923","data":{"timestamp":" 947079104921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079105046","data":{"timestamp":" 947079105045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0e7f1340-387f-4260-bb2a-e9d8b98827c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079118943","data":{"timestamp":" 947079118943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079123104","data":{"timestamp":" 947079123103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079124698","data":{"timestamp":" 947079124697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079128890","data":{"timestamp":" 947079128889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079130490","data":{"timestamp":" 947079130489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079134961","data":{"timestamp":" 947079134960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079136571","data":{"timestamp":" 947079136570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079141472","data":{"timestamp":" 947079141471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079145340","data":{"timestamp":" 947079145339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079146980","data":{"timestamp":" 947079146979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079153082","data":{"timestamp":" 947079153082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079154691","data":{"timestamp":" 947079154690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079158669","data":{"timestamp":" 947079158669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079160259","data":{"timestamp":" 947079160259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079164841","data":{"timestamp":" 947079164841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079166477","data":{"timestamp":" 947079166476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079169879","data":{"timestamp":" 947079169879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079171507","data":{"timestamp":" 947079171506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079176079","data":{"timestamp":" 947079176078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079177696","data":{"timestamp":" 947079177695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079211612","data":{"timestamp":" 947079211611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079211703","data":{"timestamp":" 947079211703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" cfe51b80-105c-40fd-b9b1-b9be623fd978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079229209","data":{"timestamp":" 947079229209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079242718","data":{"timestamp":" 947079242718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079244334","data":{"timestamp":" 947079244334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079247501","data":{"timestamp":" 947079247500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079249127","data":{"timestamp":" 947079249127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079251835","data":{"timestamp":" 947079251834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079253442","data":{"timestamp":" 947079253441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079264631","data":{"timestamp":" 947079264630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079268769","data":{"timestamp":" 947079268769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079270549","data":{"timestamp":" 947079270548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079271630","data":{"timestamp":" 947079271629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079272188","data":{"timestamp":" 947079272187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079284426","data":{"timestamp":" 947079284426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079284529","data":{"timestamp":" 947079284528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 713a3454-e58a-4597-b326-8db69a0d91e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079300007","data":{"timestamp":" 947079300006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079302851","data":{"timestamp":" 947079302850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079304485","data":{"timestamp":" 947079304484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079307083","data":{"timestamp":" 947079307082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079308713","data":{"timestamp":" 947079308712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079311393","data":{"timestamp":" 947079311393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079313023","data":{"timestamp":" 947079313022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079315568","data":{"timestamp":" 947079315568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079318382","data":{"timestamp":" 947079318381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079319974","data":{"timestamp":" 947079319974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079322671","data":{"timestamp":" 947079322671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079324278","data":{"timestamp":" 947079324277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079327145","data":{"timestamp":" 947079327145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079328720","data":{"timestamp":" 947079328720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079332698","data":{"timestamp":" 947079332698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079334338","data":{"timestamp":" 947079334337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079337027","data":{"timestamp":" 947079337027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079338630","data":{"timestamp":" 947079338630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079340991","data":{"timestamp":" 947079340991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079342575","data":{"timestamp":" 947079342574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079472132","data":{"timestamp":" 947079472131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079472205","data":{"timestamp":" 947079472204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 469b5525-989c-4c4a-8981-13ea55fc5ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079484884","data":{"timestamp":" 947079484884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-o-m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079493637","data":{"timestamp":" 947079493637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-h-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079497647","data":{"timestamp":" 947079497647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_m-r-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079505712","data":{"timestamp":" 947079505712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-i-p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079509417","data":{"timestamp":" 947079509416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-o-w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079512961","data":{"timestamp":" 947079512960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-a-m"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079520130","data":{"timestamp":" 947079520130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_v-h-t"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079525853","data":{"timestamp":" 947079525853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-f-p"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079529855","data":{"timestamp":" 947079529855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_i-v-t"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079533381","data":{"timestamp":" 947079533381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-b-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079539156","data":{"timestamp":" 947079539155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" ae107cca-9410-4dbf-b770-023da6499824"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-b-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079584316","data":{"timestamp":" 947079584316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 088ed494-ccfe-4a1c-b6f5-a41bbaa86478"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-o-w"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079588003","data":{"timestamp":" 947079588003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 088ed494-ccfe-4a1c-b6f5-a41bbaa86478"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_v-h-t"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079624162","data":{"timestamp":" 947079624161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079633028","data":{"timestamp":" 947079633027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079634660","data":{"timestamp":" 947079634659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079637482","data":{"timestamp":" 947079637482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079639078","data":{"timestamp":" 947079639077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079643437","data":{"timestamp":" 947079643437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079645044","data":{"timestamp":" 947079645043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079649115","data":{"timestamp":" 947079649114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079650737","data":{"timestamp":" 947079650737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079655496","data":{"timestamp":" 947079655495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079657096","data":{"timestamp":" 947079657095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079662443","data":{"timestamp":" 947079662442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079664051","data":{"timestamp":" 947079664050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079667350","data":{"timestamp":" 947079667349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079668980","data":{"timestamp":" 947079668979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079679554","data":{"timestamp":" 947079679554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079681192","data":{"timestamp":" 947079681191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079685656","data":{"timestamp":" 947079685655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079687273","data":{"timestamp":" 947079687273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079696388","data":{"timestamp":" 947079696381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079696471","data":{"timestamp":" 947079696471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" a672f05f-c85c-49e5-a4ff-19656f039692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079710181","data":{"timestamp":" 947079710181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079717825","data":{"timestamp":" 947079717825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079719438","data":{"timestamp":" 947079719437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079724384","data":{"timestamp":" 947079724383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079726012","data":{"timestamp":" 947079726011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079729861","data":{"timestamp":" 947079729861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079731486","data":{"timestamp":" 947079731485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079736415","data":{"timestamp":" 947079736414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079738037","data":{"timestamp":" 947079738037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079742017","data":{"timestamp":" 947079742017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079743626","data":{"timestamp":" 947079743625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079748477","data":{"timestamp":" 947079748477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079750085","data":{"timestamp":" 947079750084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079754301","data":{"timestamp":" 947079754300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079755937","data":{"timestamp":" 947079755936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079760805","data":{"timestamp":" 947079760804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079762426","data":{"timestamp":" 947079762426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079766012","data":{"timestamp":" 947079766011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079767608","data":{"timestamp":" 947079767607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079804717","data":{"timestamp":" 947079804716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079804800","data":{"timestamp":" 947079804800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 0653cc34-01bd-4c02-bbec-2f22b2739483"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079825678","data":{"timestamp":" 947079825677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TUNGULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079833109","data":{"timestamp":" 947079833109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tungule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNGULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079834746","data":{"timestamp":" 947079834746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079838257","data":{"timestamp":" 947079838257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079839854","data":{"timestamp":" 947079839854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079843345","data":{"timestamp":" 947079843344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079844945","data":{"timestamp":" 947079844944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079848406","data":{"timestamp":" 947079848405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_TABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079850516","data":{"timestamp":" 947079850515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079852142","data":{"timestamp":" 947079852142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079855165","data":{"timestamp":" 947079855163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079856769","data":{"timestamp":" 947079856769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079860005","data":{"timestamp":" 947079860005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079861622","data":{"timestamp":" 947079861622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079865282","data":{"timestamp":" 947079865282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079866904","data":{"timestamp":" 947079866903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079874221","data":{"timestamp":" 947079874220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079875838","data":{"timestamp":" 947079875837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079878455","data":{"timestamp":" 947079878455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079880083","data":{"timestamp":" 947079880082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079886319","data":{"timestamp":" 947079886318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079886388","data":{"timestamp":" 947079886388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_162806"," gameId":" 9d68d180-1713-4560-896d-fd307641c796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}